<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wholesome, Thought-Provoking Stories for Children on Noman&#39;s Tales</title>
    <link>https://nomanstales.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wholesome, Thought-Provoking Stories for Children on Noman&#39;s Tales</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nomanstales.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://nomanstales.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nomanstales.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Our Start Noman&#39;s Tales started as a single bedtime story (&#34;Four Brother Sheep&#34;) that was created to teach an important, Biblical lesson to our son. Upon further reflection, we realized that there was value in recording it for our family and others who shared our values. This realization inspired us to compile it with imagery and audio, which became the first official work of Noman&#39;s Tales, with hopefully many more to come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Links</title>
      <link>https://nomanstales.com/all-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nomanstales.com/all-links/</guid>
      <description> Books 🔗 Four Brother Sheep Shop 🔗 Etsy Store Social Media 🔗 Facebook 🔗 Instagram 🔗 YouTube 🔗 Rumble 🔗 Twitter Other 🔗 Newsletter </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://nomanstales.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nomanstales.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Loading… </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Brother Sheep - Children&#39;s Book</title>
      <link>https://nomanstales.com/books/four-brother-sheep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nomanstales.com/books/four-brother-sheep/</guid>
      <description>Four Brother Sheep Embark on a captivating adventure with the &#34;Four Brother Sheep&#34; as they learn valuable life lessons about the importance of obeying their parents. This enchanting tale follows the misadventures of four sheep siblings - Selfish, Stubborn, Pride, and Prudence - as they explore the world around them, discovering the consequences of not heeding their parents&#39; advice.
When danger lurks and their brothers are in peril, can the youngest and wisest sheep, Prudence, save the day by making the right choices?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
